Hey, stop!
Why do you bring up
such things?
It shouldn't be aired
Why? This is
a reality show
You should show
everything as it is
So everyone he liked
was a bad one?
Has he never
dated anyone properly?
No, it's not true
Don't believe him
He's just kidding
Ah!
He once fell
for a nice one
-It was me
-Hey!
Gosh, you startled me
You kept following me
when we were young
That's ancient history
And you know, I didn't
have a crush on you
Huh?
You were so cute
back then
Come on
Wow, you guys
are making me jealous
I wish I also had
a friend like you
By the way…
have we met before?
Sure, I know you
because you're
a superstar
Let's take five
What are you thinking?
I just…
I don't know
what to do now
Just take it easy
You can even
fall asleep
But…
What do you think
about today's shooting?
You didn't seem
to like me
You only chatted
with Soobin
You didn't even make
eye contact with me
Oh, did I get caught?
What?
But you also
knew Soobin
because you guys
are neighbors
Well…
I didn't know that
but I've seen him
way before that…